Fedor

Ivachev



Contact

GitHub:

github.com/FedorIvachev

WeChat:

rod iv

Email:

rod iv@outlook.com

Languages

English – C1, IELTS 7.5 Chinese – A2 Russian – native

Education

Bachelor in Applied Mathematics and Computer Science:

Computer Algebra – 2015-2019 Lomonosov Moscow State University, Moscow, Russia

Master in Computer Science:

Advanced Computing – HCI –

2019-2021

Tsinghua University, Beijing, China

Summary

Junior Computer Graphics Developer & HCI researcher. Has strong background in competitive programming, physics and math. Has developed and published Apps for iOS, Android and Tizen OS. Currently developing IoT + VR solutions.

Programming Languages: C++, C#, Python (writing regularly), Swift, Java, JavaScript, Haskell, NASM (have experience).

Tools, Libraries: Git, OpenCV, Machine learning libraries, OpenGL, Graphics Profilers, Unity, IoT automation platforms

Experience

Software Engineer - 02/2019 to 08/2019 **Huawei Technologies Co., Ltd**, Moscow

Work on the low-level Graphic Profiling Tools.

Intern- 06/2018 to 09/2018 **Samsung RC, Ltd**, Moscow

• Develop computer vision algorithms in 3D Avatar team.

Certifications

2012, 2013, 2014 - Summer Programming School 2014 - Top 100 at All-Russian Olympiad of Programming, 2014 2017 - Certificate of Practice in Web Apps Development, Samsung RC, Ltd 2020 - Huawei Certification – AI (#01010200180806249751581)

Scholarships

2018 - Full tuition for Lomonosov MSU Business School 2019 - Chinese Government Scholarship

Publications

2019 - Ivachev Fedor: Modification of Algorithm for inverting matrices with elements from ring of scalar differential operators. Collection of abstracts of the best qualifying works of CMC MSU 2019. MAKS PRESS 2019: 88 (in Russian)